[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 32, "question": "Don, what's the latest tonight?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "We're learning the latest from a source that's close to the death investigation, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "Is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "EMON: Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["California"]}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 93, "question": "How did you feel when you heard that Whitney had died, I mean, given everything we know about her lifestyle in the last few years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 94, "answer": "Well, I was in California.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Whitney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 112, "question": "I just wonder how shocking it was to people that ho knew her well?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "JJR", "WRB", "VBG", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "JJ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 113, "answer": "Very.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 130, "question": "What is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 131, "answer": "Look, I think it's not just papers, it's magazines, it's television networks, I mean CNN like everybody else has been doing a lot of coverage of this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 142, "question": "Have you spoken to any of the family?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 143, "answer": "I have.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "Do you think it's as simple as that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "Well, I'm -- all I'm saying is we don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Whitney Houston"]}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 160, "question": "Do the fans have a right to be part of this or do you think it was the sensible thing to do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 161, "answer": "Well, I think Whitney Houston came from the church.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 177, "question": "Very sadly died last -- six months ago?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VBD", "JJ", ":", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 178, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 179, "question": "And 46 years, I think, I've read that you wrote together, is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "CD", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 180, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 227, "question": "Do you think it's the right thing to do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chaka Khan"]}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 233, "question": "When you -- when you wrote, \"I'm Every Woman,\" and then you heard her sing it, has there ever been any singer that you've ever heard who could have sung it better than Whitney Houston?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "``", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 234, "answer": "You're in dangerous territory now because the song was actually written for Chaka Khan.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Whitney Houston"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 258, "question": "How would you think that she would like her legacy to be in terms of the music?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 259, "answer": "I think she will be -- you know, it's interesting.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 277, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 278, "answer": "By pure chance.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Chaka"]}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "Was it a hard decision and when you got there what was it actually like in the room?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "Well, it was a very -- I can appreciate Chaka's feelings and I respect that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBD", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "How will you remember?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "I will remember a young woman who always had a bright smile, brought joy to my life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 328, "question": "What do you mean, like trashing me in front of, like, 200 million people at the Golden Globes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "IN", ",", "IN", ",", "CD", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 329, "answer": "That was a while ago.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 334, "question": "You like jokes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 335, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 351, "question": "Isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "That's followed me around.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Hollywood"]}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 365, "question": "I was going to ask why you ask me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 366, "answer": "Well, because for a very long time you would never have imagined being in Hollywood.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "What is the reality of Hollywood excess, the type that we've seen that caused the death of Whitney Houston?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "Well, I don't know about that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Whitney Houston"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 378, "question": "Is it to not be famous too early?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 379, "answer": "Well, I think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 384, "question": "Is it a lot easier, is my point, to be older and become famous?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "CC", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 385, "answer": "Well, I think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ricky"], "LOCATION": ["Britain"]}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "It's the I can't believe my luck that I get up in the morning, have an idea, and I can start writing that idea and it will get made at the moment, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "What I can't believe is the way you look, because we all fell in love back in Britain with fat, chubby Ricky.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 399, "question": "You didn't tell me then, though, did you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", ",", "IN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "No, I didn't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 412, "question": "How much weight have you lost?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 413, "answer": "Not much at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", ":", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", ",", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 427, "question": "Hollywood smiling?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 428, "answer": "I got some free -- those things in a luxury lounge once, those -- I thought those made me gag.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "What made you go on this vanity kick?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "It wasn't a vanity kick.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "``", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", ":", "WP", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 465, "question": "Where would you be without that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "-- \"The death of a fight-useless chubby loser with -- who never cleans his teeth and stinks.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "RB", "VBD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 474, "question": "Do you get more groupies now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJR", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 475, "answer": "I don't -- never got groupies.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 476, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 477, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 483, "question": "A svelte comedic auteur or as a chubby loser?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 484, "answer": "ERVAIS: I --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["``", "NNP", ",", "''", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "History of television?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "\"Seinfeld,\" lovely show.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 565, "question": "You love Twitter, don't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 566, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "Why do you like it so much?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "I like it for lots of reasons.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ":"], "qSentId": 576, "question": "What were you getting at?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "Well, you know, as a comedian --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "EX", ":"], "qSentId": 583, "question": "-- you'd fit in well looking like that?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "Well, I thought I looked intellectual there --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 596, "question": "Always?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 597, "answer": "Of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 605, "question": "How does your -- how does your atheism, which you're passionate about -- how does that play with your American audience, given that so many people in America are God-fearing people, and probably take exception to it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", ":", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", ":", "WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "CC", "RB", "VB", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 606, "answer": "Well, but they shouldn't.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 698, "question": "Do I do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 699, "answer": "I don't think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 701, "question": "Should we play you what Steve Carell said about you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 702, "answer": "Yes, please.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve Carell"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 710, "question": "Could you do what Ricky does?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 711, "answer": "Oh, not in a million years, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ricky"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 712, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 713, "answer": "I think I would just get too skittish.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "CC", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 715, "question": "But you could play a Ricky Gervais character?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 716, "answer": "Perhaps, but to actually go in front of people and --", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ricky Gervais"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 729, "question": "ORGAN: -- you're all heart, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 730, "answer": "That's right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 740, "question": "Do you like Steve Carrell?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 741, "answer": "He's great.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve Carrell"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 772, "question": "What, with -- romantic love?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ",", "IN", ":", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 773, "answer": "I'm assuming women.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 780, "question": "Once?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 781, "answer": "Once.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 791, "question": "Why haven't you married her yet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 792, "answer": "Well, we are, really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 796, "question": "Do you think you ever will?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "."], "aSentId": 797, "answer": "Oh, I'd never say never.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 804, "question": "How do you show your romantic side?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 805, "answer": "ERVAIS: I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 824, "question": "It would be professional, really -- a moment in your life, what would it be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", ",", "RB", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 825, "answer": "There's loads of things whizzing through my head, but they're all from childhood.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 826, "question": "Like what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 827, "answer": "I just remembered one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 864, "question": "There is only one Ricky Gervais?", "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "RB", "CD", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 865, "answer": "Thank God.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ricky Gervais"]}}]